

—— Product Manager

Details

<u> eliascm1@gmail.com</u>

(+52) 551-097-9706

d 01/March/1999

in Elias Cohen

iameliascohen.com

Hard Skills

UX

UL

Agile Methodologies

SQL

Soft Skills

Leadership

Communication

Critical Thinking

Complex Problem Solving

Creativity

Languages

Spanish

(Native)

English

Profile

Experienced product manager with a passion for building exceptional products that improve customers' lives. Skilled in team building, communication, and problem-solving, with a focus on narrowing the gap between design, engineering, and business. Expert at maintaining stakeholder focus on customers' needs and working collaboratively towards the same goal.

Professional Experience

Jr. Product Manager, LeadGenius

Oct 2022 - Present, Mexico City

- Ensure a smooth Beta Test Phase by identifying, reporting, and tracking bugs encountered in the early stages of testing
- Develop and maintain key product metrics to ensure alignment with company strategies and goals
- Analyze and use metrics to make informed decisions about the product's direction
- Create easy-to-read dashboards that display critical product metrics, enabling the team to make data-driven decisions about the product's development.

Product Manager, La Frutería

July 2020 - Oct 2022, Mexico City

- Developed all processes from concept to market.
- Ensured products aligned with company strategies and goals.
- Brainstormed various marketing strategies and ways to implement them effectively.
- Successfully prioritized product requirements and set realistic expectations regarding development and timeline.

Project Manager, Selimex

July 2020 - Oct 2022, Mexico City

- Effectively determined and defined project scope and objectives.
- Utilized innovative thinking skills and problem-solving ability to develop the project.
- Collaborated with other team members to create fresh brand ideas and project initiatives.
- Developed key project goals and worked collaboratively with teams to meet those goals.

Education

Computer Science, Universidad Iberoamericana

July 2019 - Dec 2022, Mexico City